mirantis.com 2014-07-09

# Privacy Policy - Pure Play OpenStack.

This privacy policy describes Mirantis’ practices regarding how information we collect on the Mirantis web sites is used and shared with third parties. By visiting the Mirantis web sites, you accept the practices described in this privacy policy. This privacy policy applies to anonymous data and personal information collected at our web sites, and to personal information collected in connection with the sale, support and use of our products and services.

**Part I. Information Collection**

We may collect personal information through our web sites. This information is used in e-commerce transactions and to provide customer service and support.

Mirantis web sites collect personal information at several points, which can include processes associated with e-commerce, product registration, account creation and e-mail opt-in.  Visitors may voluntarily provide (and we will collect) information including: name, email address, billing and shipping information, product purchase information, and/or product registration information.

We also collect the personal information that is provided by visitors who submit it through our web sites.

We may collect information related to the use of our web sites – through, for example, the use of cookies – in order to better understand our customers’ needs. A cookie is a small text file that our web server places on your computer hard drive that includes a unique identifier. Cookies enable us to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users.  We may also use web bugs, clear gifs and similar technologies that collect data similar to that collected by a cookie.

If you do not wish Mirantis to use your personal information as described in this section, please follow the procedure in Part III (Access to Your Information) below.

In order to protect the privacy interests of younger Internet users, we do not actively market our web sites or products to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 for marketing purposes. We encourage children of any age to visit our web sites or to use our products and services only with the supervision of their parents.

**Part II. Information Usage**

The information collected by us is used to understand how customers are using our products and services in order to make them better.

Anonymous, aggregated data is analyzed on a regular basis to understand product use and quality, feature popularity, quality, and to assist in the design of future products and services.

Personal information is used to fulfill orders, provide customer support, and for marketing purposes such as email announcements of new products or offers. We provide an option for you to choose not to receive marketing communications and you may always contact us at info[at]mirantis.com to opt-out of marketing communications (however, we reserve the right to use your contact information if we consider it necessary to send you crucial information about the product or services you have purchased from us.)

We may also share information with companies integral to the use of the product or service.  In those cases, the use of that information is subject to the privacy policies of the receiving party.

We may use third parties (including contractors and service providers) to help with certain aspects of our operations, which may require disclosure of your personal information to them. For example, we may use a third party to communicate with you (via telephone, email, or letter) about our products or services, to send information to you, to process and collect payment via your credit card (if applicable), and to perform other work that we may need to outsource. We require these contractors and third parties to use your personal information only as necessary to perform the services they are asked to perform.

We may share some or all of your personal information with our current or future “affiliates” (which means a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control), in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this privacy policy. If another company acquires Mirantis (or a business unit of Mirantis that uses your personal information), that company will possess the personal information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

We offer links to other web sites. Please note: those other web sites may observe privacy standards different from ours and the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policies on those other sites.

Our web sites offer a space for postings and submissions. Please be advised that any information posted in these venues will be publicly available.

Finally, please be assured that we do not sell information collected from customers.

**Part III. Access to Your Information**

If you wish to correct or delete of any of your personal information held by us or a change in the way we use your information, please contact info[at]mirantis.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to fulfill your request in a timely manner, but not more than 30 days. However, even if we delete such personal information from our ‘live’ database, it may still be stored on other databases (including those kept for archival purposes).

**Part IV. Data Storage and Security**

We use industry-standard methods of securing electronic databases of personal information. Except as provided elsewhere in this privacy policy, we limit access to personal information in electronic databases to those persons in our organization who have a business need for such access. However, you should know that no web site operator, including Mirantis, can fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information.

Your privacy is very important to us. Due to factors beyond our control, however, we cannot fully ensure that your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties other than those mentioned above. For example, we may be legally required to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

**Part V. Modifications**

We may amend this privacy policy at any time by posting the amended version on our web sites.

**Part VI. Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact info[at]mirantis.com . We will use commercially reasonable efforts to resolve disputes within 90 days.
